

CONTACT

- **1** 0491632234
- mathiaswouters.netlify.app
- 🖒 Oud-Turnhout, Belgium
- in LinedIn
- <u>Twitter</u>

MATHIAS WOUTERS

CLOUD & CYBER SECURITY STUDENT

ABOUT ME

My name is Mathias Wouters, and I'm 21 years old. Currently, I'm studying Cloud and Cyber Security. I am social, friendly, stressresistant, responsible, and ambitious. In my free time, I like to read books and keep myself busy with new technologies.

EDUCATION

Thomas More, Geel | 2021 - now Bachelor Cloud & Cyber Security

HT20, Turnhout | 2019 - 2021 **Electromechanics**

Sint-Pietersinstituut, Turnhout | 2014 - 2019

Mathematics & Sciences

EXPERIENCES

Job student | 2017 - 2023

Colruyt

- Help customers
- Fill shelves
- Working at the cash register

Job student | 2023 - now

Get Driven

80%

70%

- Professional customer interaction
- Providing chauffeur services
- Responsible handling of customers/vehicles

HOBBIES

Scout leader

Traveling

Reading books

SKILLS

Linux 85%
Cloud (AWS - Azure) 75%
Kubernetes & Docker 75%

Python

Cisco Networking

Windows

LANGUAGES

Dutch - Mother tongue

English - C1

French - B1

German - A1